let me take you to a place
nestled among the mountain slopes where
glaciers weep the spring away
and the birds sing
[Music]
you can find me where the fairies are
disguised in a splendor of silver wings
they flit then dive among the
huckleberries
and make love in the grass
[Music]
watch how the boughs nod heavy with
fruit
the sweet tang melts into my daydreams
[Music]
though the summer is nearly at an end my
lips are stained
in spirit light anticipating the sunset
of the season and the dawning of the
next
have you ever been called an old soul
maybe
wild child i have and it made me feel
as if i was unusual or that maybe i
didn't quite fit
into the ideals of a modern world
but i came to see that the opposite is
true that there are many
old souls thriving right now sharing
their love of nature
history and craftsmanship with the world
[Music]
they are not out of place but actively
inspiring a future where we value the
earth as it should be
and embrace simple living over
conspicuous consumption
you can be an old soul that thrives in a
modern world
simply by choosing hope over despair
attuning yourself to nature
and embodying what inspires you it all
begins and ends with you
you are enough that is where you can
make the greatest impact and connection
that is all you need to do
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
do
no
[Music]
you